{"data":[{"question":"I start work _____ 8.30 every morning.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"My birthday is _____ March.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Dieter went to the cinema _____ Monday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":" I like to go skiing _____ winter.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Are you doing anything special _____ New Year?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Julia goes to her fitness class _____ Tuesdays.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Children like to get up early _____ Christmas Day.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"Michael was born _____ 1962.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"The plane is due to arrive ______ 19.25","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"},{"question":"The conference is _____ 6 June.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"2"}]}